{
    "id": "ac98a30e2fc74a988365ff3e32fdd253",
    "title": "Grammar exercise: conjunctions and transitional adverbs",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6324e64d8da34add84bbd91e835ce94b",
            "title": "Conjunctions And Transitional Adverbs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She was late …………………. we went without her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "so",
                        "thus"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… I fired at the tiger, he shook my arm.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "Until",
                        "Because"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am glad ………………… tomorrow is a holiday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "though",
                        "so",
                        "because"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was angry …………………. I said nothing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "therefore",
                        "hence"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Vegetables are essential for good health ………………… you must include them in your diet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "since",
                        "therefore"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… you lose your job, what will you do?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Supposing",
                        "Supposing if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He must be punished ………………… he does not try.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "so long as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is intelligent ………………….. he gets good marks.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "as",
                        "because"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. he was late he missed the train.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "So",
                        "Therefore",
                        "Because"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was a big argument about ………………. we should sell our new house.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "weather",
                        "whether"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}